>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 有些人可能想知道
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Some of
you may be wondering,
那箭的功能呢
well what about arrow functions?
我们在 ES6 中加入的最喜欢的功能是谁知道
That favorite feature that we've
added to ES6 for who knows how long,
我的意思是，谁知道人们一直在要求这个箭头的功能，但是
I mean who knows how long people have
been asking for this arrow function, but
终于在 ES6降落了
it finally landed in ES6.
我想知道布兰登 - 艾克想做的
I like to imagine that maybe
Brendan Ike wanted to do that
在原型机里它只花了他 15 年的时间
in the original prototypes, and
it just took him 15 years or whatever.
但箭功能于六年后到达。
But arrow functions arrived
in year six a few years back.
就像云彩打开天神在我们的基础上，如果你愿意的话
And it is as if the clouds opened and
heaven shone down upon us, if you will,
人们似乎正走向这个新的启蒙运动
that people just seemed to move to
this new level of enlightenment and
当他们得到箭的功能时就会喜欢和喜欢的语言
love and joy for the language
once they got the arrow function.
你在这里看到第 1 行箭头函数在数学中的用法
You see here on line 1, the usage
of an arrow function in the math,
与名称函数表达式相反。
as opposed to a name function expression.
所以你在想，凯尔，你对箭功能有什么感觉 ?
So you're wondering, hey Kyle,
what's your feeling about arrow functions?
我的反应是，箭头函数是匿名的。
And my response is,
arrow functions are anonymous.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我认为您不应该使用匿名函数表达式，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I don't think you should
use anonymous function expressions,
我想你可以做数学
I think you can do the math.
我觉得你不该用箭的功能
I don't think you ought to
be using arrow functions.
当然我不认为你应该用箭的一般功能
Certainly I don't think you should be
using arrow functions as a general
替换所有其他功能。
replacement for all other functions.
你不应该仅仅因为它们是简洁而简洁的语法而使用它们。
You shouldn't be using them just because
they're nice and short, concise syntax.
这不是他们创造的原因那只是其中的一个特征
That isn't why they were created,
that's only one of the characteristics
也许我认为这甚至不是主要特征
that maybe I think could be argued
not even the primary characteristic.
方法的语法越短，
The shorter the syntax by the way,
语法的角个案越复杂。
the more complex the corner
cases of syntax are.
如果你有过不同的角力
And if you've ever wrangled
various different corner cases,
在箭头函数语法上存在 15 个不同的变体。
there is like 15 different variations
on the arrow function syntax.
所以不是没有成本的。
So doesn't come without a cost.
但我想告诉你唯一能找到第 1 行的方法
But I would tell you that the only way
looking at line 1 that you can figure out
该错误函数正在执行的操作是读取它的函数体。
what that error function is doing,
is to read it's function body.
但是当我读函数名时，我不需要读任何代码。
But when I read the function name
I don't need to read any code.
那里有一个英文名，告诉我该函数的用途。
There's one English name there that
tells me the purpose of that function.
很多人跟我争论说
A lot of people argue with me and say,
第 1 行的箭头功能是完全显而易见的。
the arrow function on line 1
is completely self obvious.
也许它是显而易见的，但还是一个推论。
Maybe it is self obvious, but
it is still an inference.
你还需要从代码中推断
You are still having to infer
the purpose of that from the code,
而不是看到被列出的目的
rather than seeing the purpose listed out.
如果我给出更好的名字，我在幻灯片上节省了空间。
And if I gave an even better name,
I was saving space on the slides.
但是，如果我给出更好的名称，例如获取人员标识或获取缺省人员标识。
But if I gave an even better name like
get person ID or get default person id.
我可以把更多的信息在语义上告诉读者
I can put lots of more information in
there that semantically tells the reader
它的目的是什么在代码上是不明显的
of my code what its purpose is,
that would not be obvious in the code.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，我的操作是，不要将箭头功能用于此用途。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So, my take is, don't
use arrow functions for this purpose.
稍后我们将返回箭头函数，您将看到其中的一个和
Later in the course we will come back to
arrow functions and you'll see the one and
只有一个例外的情况是我对箭式功能有规律
only one exception that I have
to the arrow functions rule,
这就是他们的词法
which is their lexical this behavior.
但我不赞同或建议
But I do not endorse or recommend or
建议将其用作任何功能的常规替换。
suggest using them as a general
replacement for any function.
>> Kyle Simpson: 短或长?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Short or long?
又一个例子，如果你做了承诺链，我不是承诺的大粉丝。
Another example, if you've done promise
chains, I'm not a big fan of promise
但是如果你喜欢做承诺链
chains anyway, but
if you like to do promise chains,
这是您经常在这些功能中进行解析的另一种情况。
this is another case where you often
will just parse in these functions.
这里有一个地方即使我之前被问到
Here's one of these places where even
though, that I was asked earlier,
我可能倾向于我的规则，因为这是在第 14 行上的一个衬。
I might tend for my rule because
this is a one liner on line 14.
我可能倾向于作为内联函数表达式执行此操作，
I might tend to do that as
an inline function expression,
因为我真的很不喜欢保证链的可读性
because I really dislike the readability
of promise chain so much.
我觉得他们很难看，很喜欢意大利面，很像 jQuery
I find them very hard to read and very
spaghetti-ish, very much like the jQuery
大家都说我们几年前就不应该这么做了
code that everybody said we shouldn't
be doing several years back.
我觉得铁链的风格是一样的
I find promise chains to
be in that same style.
我以前很喜欢那种风格现在我很不喜欢那种风格
And I used to be in love with that style,
and now I very much dislike that style,
从可读性的角度来看
from a readability perspective primarily.
所以尽管我通常会有一条规则把它作为内联
So even though I might normally have
a rule where I would pass it as an inline
函数表达式。
function expression.
在这个案件中
In this particular case,
我可能把那个功能拉出来作为一个功能声明，
I would probably pull that function
out as a function declaration, and
所以承诺链会有你在第 11 行上看到的东西
therefore the promise chain would have
something like you see on line 11,
它正在按名称来引用函数，而不是函数表达式。
which is referencing a function by name,
instead of a function expression at all.
但我仍然不会像你在第 10 行上看到的那样使用箭头功能。
But I still wouldn't use the arrow
function like you see on line 10.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在，有些人说，他们是匿名的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now, some people
have said, well, they're anonymous,
但你还是可以把它们分配给变量
but you can still assign
them to variables and
从他们的利益中得到了同样的好处对吧
get almost the same benefit out of them,
right?
我可以执行此 getId 并将其指定为名为 getId 的变量，并且
I can take this getId and
assign it a variable called getId, and
那我就用 " people.map"
then I'm using people.map.
第 2 行确实有一个叫 getId的名字。
And it's true that the line 2 definitely
does have a name in it called getId.
但如果你去做第 1 行的麻烦
But if you went to the trouble
to do line 1, guess what,
功能声明的字符实际上较少。
it's actually fewer characters
to do the function declaration.
你为什么要特别用一个康斯特的方式
Why do you go to all the trouble
especially by the way if you use a const,
还长了两个字
it's two more characters long.
如果你算算，实际花费的是多或多的字符
If you do the math, you're actually
spending as much or more characters
以这种方式定义函数，而不是将其作为函数声明来定义。
to define the function that way, rather
than doing it as a function declaration.
所以我不明白为什么人们都被困在这里
So I just don't see any reason why people
are stuck on this,other than almost
我们可以写更简明的代码
an emotional attachment to this idea
that we can write more concise code.
请猜测，更简洁的代码不会自动等同更多可读代码。
Guess what, more concise code does not
automatically equal more readable code.
在某些情况下，它确实存在，但在许多其他情况下，它不存在。
In some cases, it does, but
in many other cases, it doesn't.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所以我对箭头的评价非常不受欢迎
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So there's my really
super unpopular opinion on arrow
功能，只是一些思考的食物。
functions, just some food for thought.